Muhammad Fadhil Hidayatullah

College Student

+6282299227661 fgeminni0@gmail.com Denpasar, Indonesia



SUMMARY

An undergraduate student of Informatics Engineering at Bíawijaya Univeísity that is a knowledge-curious, teamwork, communicative, and quick learner person. I have interest in Front-End Web Developer, Full Stack Web Developer, Apple iOS Developer, Andíoid Developer, Ul Design, and UX Researcher.

EDUCATION

2020 – 2024 (Expected) Brawijaya Univerisity

Bachelor's degree, Informatics Engineering

CGPA 3.87

2016 - 2017 Situbondo 1 State High School

High school diploma, Mathematics and Natural Science

EXPERIENCE

02/2022 - Present EMIF FILKOM UB

Co-Head of Student Welfare and Advocacy

06/2021 - 11/2021 IF ELSE FILKOM UB

Staff Companion

02/2023 - 06/2023 M-KNOWS CONSULTING

iOS Developer Intern

PROJECT

11/2022 CafeQ

(Product Development) Mobile application for book a café in Malang, Indonesia. I am

as a UI/UX designer in this project.

11/2022 Domalink

(UX Research) Mobile application for student to make an appointment with the

lecturer. I am as a UI/UX designer in this project.

11/2022 CafeQ

(Android Application) Android application for book a café in Malang, Indonesia. User

can see the near café, information about a café, café rating, and available table to

book.

05/2022 Student Repo

(Website) Learning video and learning module are provided in this website. Student also can post a learning video and learning module at this website. This website

implements HTML, CSS, and CRUD. I am as a UI/UX designer in this project.

11/2022 FavFood's

(iOS Application) FavFood's is a user-friendly iOS app connecting you to a wide

variety of local eateries for quick and easy food and drink orders. Browse extensive

menus, and customize your order.

02/2023 Sarang Dating App

(Multi Platform Application) Sarang App is a dating apps that offering a streamlined dating experience with advanced matching and secure chatting. Find genuine

connections and embark on your journey to love with ease.

02/2023 KampusGratis

(Multi Platform Application) KampusGratis is an e-learning management system that records reports of student learning improvement or progress. KampusGratis is the first free higher education platform in Indonesia. providing easy access to learning for everyone without any prerequisites.

04/2023 Find House App

(Multi Platform Application) Discover your ideal boarding house with Find House, a user-friendly app offering extensive listings and easy navigation. Filter by location, price, and amenities to quickly find a comfortable and affordable living space. Find House makes your search for house

straightforward and hassle-free.

CERTIFICATES

11/2022 – 12/2022	SwiftUI & iOS Engineer: The Complete App Development Bootcamp BuildWithAngga
02/2023 - 03/2023	Flutter App Developer: Bikin Aplikasi Tinder Cari BuildWithAngga
03/2023 – 04/2023	State Management Bloc Flutter Course Udemy
04/2023 – 05/2023	Dart & Flutter Development Bootcamp: Find House App BuildWithAngga
06/2023 – 07/2023	Dart Programming Bootcamp dari Buildwithangga BuildWithAngga
06/2023 – 07/2023	Flutter Mobile Apps Course dari Buildwithangga BuildWithAngga
06/2023 – 07/2023	Flutter Developer: Basic State Management dari Buildwithangga BuildWithAngga

SKILLS

Hard Skill

- Python
- Java
- Swift
- HTML & CSS
- UI Design (Figma)
- Office (Word, Excel, and PowerPoint)

Soft Skill

- Problem Solving
- Work Ethic
- Creativity
- Communication
- Public Speaking

- Kotlin
- Dart
- Flutter
- Critical Thinking
- Analytical Thinking
- Teamwork
- Initiative
- Presentation

LANGUAGES

Native Indonesian

Intermediate English